<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="question_1">Q: What does this app do?</string>
    <string name="question_2">Q: How to get started?</string>
    <string name="question_3">Q: How can I share data?\nWhat can I share?</string>
    <string name="question_4">Q: Can I use one RuuviTag for multiple spaces?</string>
    <string name="question_5">Q: Who made this app?</string>
    <string name="question_6">Q: I have another question or have feedback/bug issue.</string>

    <string name="answer_1">
        A: In this app, you can add spaces of any area,
        for example your kitchen, balcony and summer cottage,
        individually measure circumstance data (temperature, air pressure and humidity) from them and
        share them among other users.
    </string>
    <string name="answer_2">
        A: Start by adding spaces from the spaces page. After that,
        head to measure page and choose which space to measure from.
        A RuuviTag measuring device is used to measure conditions of selected space.
        You must add one to each space by clicking the Bluetooth Icon on spaces page or measure page.
    </string>
    <string name="answer_3">
        A: Head to the measure page. There, you can see your properties and select a space from a property.
        Select a clock symbol from the space list.
        Add a schedule and when the scheduled measurement is done,
        click on the finished schedule to get the results.
        There you can share the results from the top bar\'s share symbol.
    </string>
    <string name="answer_4">
        A: Yes. However, note that you can\'t save data from two spaces that use the same device at the same time.
    </string>
    <string name="answer_5">
        A: This app is developed by Mikael Holm and Tiitus Telke
        of Metropolia University of Applied Sciences as a part of Mobile solutions major program.
    </string>
    <string name="answer_6">
        A: Please send us email to tiitus.telke\@metropolia.fi. We are happy to help you \u263A.
    </string>
</resources>